well well well if it isn't Inuyasha
I thought you learned your lesson the
last time I saw you or perhaps you need
to be taught another lesson should I
beat your ass just like I did your
brother I'm in search of the final
shikon jewel shard and I heard that you
might know where it is which you will
tell me of its location if not then you
will die do I make myself clear Sonic
that's an interesting proposal but I
have a better one you let me finish
going Peepli and maybe I won't kill you
after I am done how does that sound big
boy
that's fine take your time I'm enjoying
the view back here now let's [ __ ] do
this
now you die Sonic
this is what happens when you challenge
someone like me
ha nothing personal kicked Oh Moira
moose indeed oh honey you dropped your
guard all according to keikaku
[Music]